Trickster Raccoon Dog
Brought to you by: Ko-Fi.me/OrangeFlash
I finished drawing!
Suneo, show me your sketch.
Ah, it's you, Giant!
Have a look.
Looks so good.
Show me your sketch, Giant.
See?
What's this?
An Elephant!
I'd expect nothing less from you, Giant.
It's huge and strong, just like you.
I know, right?
Ah, Shizuka-chan!
What did you sketch?
Me?
Here, have a look at my sketch.
Flamingo Couple, huh? Wow!
Awesome!
Indeed!
Oh no! You guys are flattering me.
BTW, where is that Nobita and what's he up to?
He's probably still drawing, he's such a slowpoke!
I knew it, he hasn't finished his sketch.
Please don't move!
Nobita-san, how's your drawing?
Oh, you guys!
It isn't standing still at all, so my sketch is unfinished.
Ah, a Cat? How cute!
But it's a Raccoon Dog.
Oi, Nobita!
Yes?
I see, that's it!
What's up, Suneo?
In fact, I've always thought that Nobita's face resembled....
My face?
Like what?
Like a Raccoon Dog!
Raccoon Dog?
Raccoon Dog, right!
I know, right?
Don't play tricks on us, Nobita!
Stop it, Suneo!
But you laughed as well!
All of you didn't have to make fool out of me, you know!
What, a Raccoon Dog, they say?
How mean! They went way too much overboard this time!
I won't forgive them! I will make them pay!
Calm down, I was the one who's made fun of, not you.
Aren't you angry at being called as a Raccoon Dog?
Of course I'm! After all, Suneo made fun of me!
Alright, let's punish Suneo!
Raccoon Dog!
How mean of you, you also think I'm a Raccoon Dog?
Nope, this is the gadget which trick others.
Oh?
You must have heard of the Shape-shifting Raccoon Dogs...
On foot of mountain, turning noon into night, misleading people....
Making inedible stuff feels like it's edible.
Can this gadget easily trick people?
Yep, it's used in Haunted Parks in 22nd Century to fool people.
Reality feels like an alternative world.
Sounds so cool!
Did I wear it correctly?
Yep!
What are you doing, Nobita?
Oh, it's Mum!
I'll play a trick on Mum...
Nobita, have some snack-...
I've brought your favorite Dorayaki for you, Lord Doraemon.
I'll be leaving now...
Mum was fooled completely.
Mum perceived me as a king!
This gadget is so cool!
After eating Dorayaki, let's go look for Suneo!
I'll get you fooled, Suneo!
It's Suneo!
I bought new intense Manga...
but Nobita's Raccoon Dog face distracts me...
it makes manga less funny.
Just you wait and see, Suneo!
Oh yeah, I was on the way...
I must hurry!
He was made fool of!
I'm lost at this forest at the foothill!
Oh no, a Wolf! Someone please save me!
Please save me from this wolf!
He's so scared!
Suneo is perceiving the puppy as a wolf!
Phew! I'm saved!
Huh? Where am I?
I'm in the middle of nowhere!
I feel something off!
Don't scare me!
It's become night only in a second.
I'm shivering, I must find a warm shelter!
What now?
Got you!
Ah, there's a mansion! I'm saved!
I'll stay here overnight!
Pardon me!
Anybody home?
Welcome, Young Master Suneo.
Excuse me, I'd like to stay here for night.
What are you talking about? Hurry, dig in.
Please have a rest!
Thanks very much!
I'm saved! I'm warm and hungry!
I wonder what's the dinner?
Huh? Sound of a knife?
He must be so tasty!
Oh no, she's the Mountain Hag!
What now?
Hold it!
She's gonna eat me!
What's wrong, Suneo?
How great! We fooled Suneo completely.
Now gimme back my gadget.
Please lend it to me for a while.
How helpless! Ok, but only for a while.
Don't get full of yourself.
Don't worry! See ya!
I wonder if he's gonna be alright?
Knowing him...
Oh well, hope he'll manage it!
Hey, Nobita, what are you up to?
Hah, you are a Raccoon Dog!
Alright, I'll teach you a lesson!
I see, I was in middle of a journey...
Oh, Suneo, here you are.
Giant, glad I found you!
I'm hungry, let's go look for food.
They don't even know that they are being fooled.
Ah, Sat-chan!
Oh, Sis!
What are you doing?
Let's play Mummy game together.
It's boring all by myself.
Sure, I'll play with you, but only for a short while.
Look, there's a tea vendor. We're saved!
Let's dig in!
Welcome!
Will you guys join us in Mummy game?
I'd like to have dumplings!
Dumpling made out of flower!
Thanks, I'm digging in!
Are you serious, Takeshi-san?
I'll have these Manjuu.
Tasty!
Unbelievable, he's eating it!
Instead of dumplings, I'll have Manjuu too.
How yum!
Are you guys making fool of us?
I'm stuffed. Thanks for the treat.
How mean!
How will you make up for my shopping?
Oh no! I forgot to tell Nobita how to deactivate the Raccoon Dog!
I'm so full!
Look, Giant, there's a hot spring.
Right!
Let's take a warm rest!
What are you guys up to?
Feels so good!
I tricked them to perceive the park pond as an hot spring! Haha!
Can I join you guys?
Sure, hop in!
Feels so warm!
Stop it, you guys!
Ah, it's Shizuka-chan's voice. Wonder what's wrong?
what's the matter, Shizuka-chan?
Look!
i'm feeling so relaxed.
True!
Suneo and Giant being there like that is not surprising...
But why is even Nobita-kun with them?
Why are you making a fool out of yourself, Nobita-kun?